{
    "subject": "resource/Argyro_Strataki",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Heraklion",
    "human_readable": "Argyro Strataki was born in Heraklion.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8863982558250427,
            "question": "Where was Argyro Strataki born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7413623332977295,
            "question": "Name a city on the island where Argyro Strataki was born."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6972928047180176,
            "question": "Are there any famous people from Heraklion besides Argyro Strataki?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38491103053092957,
            "question": "Is Argyro Strataki from Greece?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3836106061935425,
            "question": "What is Heraklion known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2868211269378662,
            "question": "Does Argyro Strataki have any notable achievements?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28244748711586,
            "question": "What is the history of Heraklion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23374232649803162,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Heraklion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22229495644569397,
            "question": "What is the climate like in Heraklion?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16901163756847382,
            "question": "What are some popular tourist destinations in Heraklion?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Argyro Strataki was born in Heraklion.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3258_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the climate like in Heraklion?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3258_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Heraklion?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3258_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the history of Heraklion?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3258_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3258_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3258_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3258_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3258_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3258_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3258_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3258_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3258_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3258_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3258_42.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Argyro Strataki was born in Heraklion.\" Specifically, both `21.txt` and `39.txt` mention her place of birth as Heraklion."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}